(Sheldon:)Thank you.
But you said
you might introduce me to him...
I'm free on Thursday.
(Bernadette:)Hey, hey,
they're leaving.
(Penny:)What? Here,
give me, give me.
(Penny:)Oh, my God. Oh, my God,
they're coming right towards us.
(Bernadette:)We got to get out of here.
Okay. Well, wait, what about Leonard?
(Bernadette:)He and his tiny bladder
can take the bus!
(starts engine)
(both gasp)
Oh, no!
(turns off engine)
She just hit my car!
(Amy:)What are you guys
doing here?
Oh! Hey, Ames!
What are you doing here?
LEONARD:
What happened?
OMG!
(Penny:)Aren't you
Leonard Hofstadter?
(Sheldon:)Yeah.
(Dave:)I saw you speak at Stanford
with Sheldon Cooper!
(Dave:)Amy, can you believe it?
It's Dr. Leonard Hofstadter!
(Amy:)No. Pinch me.
(Dave:)It's an absolute pleasure to meet you.
Can I shake your hand?
(Leonard:)I don't know if you want
to do that... I was just...